好
Okay.
在Dan介绍数据库之前
So before Dan gets carried away with databases, let's look at
让我们看看当你用intent在activity之间切换的时候都会发生什么
what happens when you use an intent to transition between activities.
在Sunshine应用中
Within Sunshine,
如果你点击Activity列表中的一个Activity  它会打开这个更加详细的Activity
if you tap on a list in the main activity it opens up the detail activity.
但是主Activity还是在后台运行的
But the main activity remains on the backstack.
随时都准备着重新在前台显示  只要你点一下返回键  主Activity就会重新显示
Ready to reappear as soon as you hit Back.
那么现在  在这个例子中  两个Activity在同一个应用中
Now, in that example, both activities are within the same app.
但是  像我们在第三节中学习的一样  你还可以使用浏览器浏览网页
But as we learned in lesson three, you can also watch the browser or
使用Sunshine里的地图应用
maps app from sunshine.
而且  用户可以点Home键回到主界面
Or for that matter, the user can hit Home.
并开启其他的应用  或者点Recent键
And launch apps from there, or they can use the recent key or
或者在通知栏中转换到其他的应用
switch to another app using notifications.
这些行为都意味着你可以终止在后台运行的很多应用
All of these options mean you can end up with a lot of apps on your back stack.
一定要记住移动设备的资源是非常有限的
Now, keep in mind that our resources on devices are extremely limited.
所以让很多的应用在后台等待不是一个好办法
So it's not a good idea to have dozens of apps sitting idle in the background.
Android为我们解决了这个问题
Android solves this for us,
所以你不必使用那些令人讨厌的杀进程的应用
so you don't have to use those awful task killer apps.
那么  这些是怎么做到的呢
So, how does it do that?
其实是系统会杀掉那些低优先级的你目前没有在使用的应用
Well, it kills low priority applications that you haven't used in a while.
在第六节课  我们会仔细的讲解Android是如何找出哪些应用应该被杀掉的
We'll go into detail on exactly how it figures out which app needs to die, in lesson six.
现在  你只要知道你的应用
But for now, it's important to realize that your app isn't in
无法控制自己什么时候被销毁就好了
control of its own destiny.
你的应用可能在任何时间被杀死
It can be killed at any time.
所以你要学会如何处理这种情况
So you need to know, how to deal with that.
这就意味着你要了解Activity的生命周期
And that means understanding the lifecycle of an activity and the signals we
和在系统中获得的表示生命周期状态的信号
get from the framework to indicate its progress through the lifetime.